Come on,no peeking.
不能偷看喔
Our eyes are closed,and we're crossing the street. Very good.
我們要閉眼睛過馬路，太好了
Okay. Open up!
好，可以看了
What do you want to show us?
你們是要我們看什麼？
Because all I can see is this bitchen van!
我只看到…超炫的廂型車！
It's for our catering business.
這是我們做外燴的專用車
I think I know that girl.
我好像認識那女孩
We won't keep it this way,though.
但最後不會是這樣 不會嗎？
We'll replace the sword with a baguette.
我們會把寶刀換成法國麵包
Oh,my God,I think I lost my virginity in that van.
天啊，我的第一次 好像就是在廂型車裡
Also,we don't know what to do with this.
還有這個也不知道要怎麼處理
Oh yeah,I definitely know her.
對，我一定認識她
The One Where They're Going To Party!
本集播出：「狂歡之王」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Remember that guy from cooking school that put cilantro in everything?
還記得我說過那個在烹飪學校 煮什麼都加香菜的人嗎？
Sure,Cilantro Larry!
記得，香菜賴瑞嘛
I'm filling in for him as food critic for the Chelsea Reporter.
我要替他代班 幫赤爾夕通訊報做美食評鑒
What an amazing opportunity to influence...
摩妮卡，這可是大好機會呢 你能影響到…
...dozens of people!
二、三十個人呢
What about our catering business?
那我們的外燴生意怎麼辦？
It's just one night a week.
我這個一星期只要一個晚上
Plus,I get to take you out for free dinners.
我還能帶你們到處去吃免錢的
Well,in that case....
既然是那樣的話…
That was me,hopping on board.
剛才是我在上車一起去
Hey,guys. Hey,Ross!
大夥兒好，羅斯？
Quick question for you.
快問快答
Are you ready to party?
你準備好要狂歡沒？
I could maybe go out for a couple of beers.
沒有，出去喝幾杯啤酒或許行
There's this thing about bees on the Discovery Channel.
但是今晚發現頻道要演大黃蜂
I don't think you heard me. Are you ready...
你可能沒聽清楚 你準備好要…
...to party?
狂歡沒？
No.
不會吧
Gandalf? Gandalf is coming to town?
甘道夫要來？
I have nothing to do,so tomorrow we are partying with Gandalf,dude!
兄弟，反正我女友不在沒事幹 明天我們去跟甘道夫狂歡吧！
Dude,we are so going to party!
兄弟，我們要去狂歡了耶
Wow,okay. Dude alert!
好吧，兄弟請注意
Who is this guy?
這個人是誰？
Mike "Gandalf" Ganderson. Only the funnest guy in the world.
麥克甘道夫 世界上最爆笑的人
I'll call to get off work tomorrow.
我要打給公司說明天請假
I'll call after you!
你打完換我
This will be so cool! We never party anymore.
兄弟，這一定超酷的 我們八百年沒狂歡了
Were you smoking something in the back of our van?
你們是不是躲在廂型車裡 偷抽了大麻？
"We never have fun anymore"? You have fun with me.
是啊，什麼叫八百年沒狂歡 跟我在一起就很樂啊
Remember those strippers? And you paid me $50 to eat that book?
記得去看脫衣舞那回？ 你們給我50美元要我吞書
You are going to love this guy. Gandalf is the party wizard.
喬伊，這個人你一定喜歡 甘道夫是狂歡巫師喔
Why do you call him "Gandalf"?
你們幹嘛叫他「甘道夫」？
Gandalf the Wizard.
巫師甘道夫啊
Didn't you read Lord of the Rings in high school?
你念高中沒看過「魔戒」？
No,I had sex in high school.
沒，但我念高中有上過床
Joanna? I was wondering if I could ask you something.
喬安娜，有件事想請問一下
There's an opening for a buyer in Junior Miss
少淑女服飾的採購助理有空缺
-That'd be a step down for me. -Actually,I meant for me.
那我豈不是連降三級了？ 不是啦，我是毛遂自薦
The hiring committee is meeting people all day and....
招聘委員會每天都在面試…
I guess you can't stay my assistant forever.
我很希望我能拒絕 但總不能讓你永遠當我助理吧
Neither can you,Sophie, but for different reasons.
蘇菲，你也是，但理由不同
I'm so glad you don't have a problem. If you did,I wouldn't apply.
真高興你完全沒有意見 否則我壓根不會想去報考
In that case
真的啊，那樣的話…
That's why I'm glad there's no problem.
所以我才很高興你沒意見
I'm on the hiring committee, so there'll be one friendly face.
沒關係，其實我也是面試人員 你起碼能看到一張友善的臉
That's great!
這真是太棒了
Junior Miss is where I started.
我也是從少淑女部起家的
I slept with the ugliest guy to get that job.
跟個一級醜男上床 才得到那份工作
-Really? -No.
這樣啊？ 開玩笑的啦
Yeah.
有
I mean,no.
話說回來…沒有啦
With your qualifications,you won't need to sleep with some guy.
別擔心，以你的資歷 不用出賣肉體也能被錄取
Although I might need some convincing.
雖然我可能要驗貨確定一下
Kidding!
逗你的啦
God,I feel wild today!
天啊，我今天真亢奮
Man,I am so excited, I may vomit.
要命，我興奮到都快吐了
Will you calm down? He's just a human guy.
你興奮個什麼勁？ 他不過就是個人嘛
You don't understand. He's amazing.
你有所不知，甘道夫超神的
You never know what'll happen.
跟他出去可是驚喜連連
You go out for beer and end up on a boat to Nova Scotia.
幾杯啤酒下肚 醒來竟然正在坐漁船去加拿大
-Really? -It's beautiful country up there.
真的？ 對，那裡風景很美
Hey. Okay.
好
I got my passport,fresh socks, and a snakebite kit.
我帶了護照，乾淨的襪子 還有蛇毒解藥
It won't be exactly like last time.
這次不會跟上次完全一樣啦
I'll see you guys.
回頭見了
I have an audition, but I'll meet you.
我要先去試鏡 晚點一定去跟你們會合
Where will you be around noon?
你們中午左右會在哪裡？
Somewhere maybe along the equator?
差不多在赤道附近吧
好
Hello.
It's Gandalf!
甘道夫打來的！
So are you in town?
你已經到了？
Oh,well....
Maybe next time,then.
那就下次再約吧
What happened?
怎麼了？
He can't come. He's stuck in Chicago.
他在芝加哥耽擱，沒辦法來
Oh,man!
要命
Chicago's so lucky.
芝加哥真是太走運了
Stupid,useless...
真是愚蠢又沒有用的…
...Canadian money!
加拿大錢
You have a very impressive resume, Miss Greene.
葛林小姐，你的履歷非常精彩
I especially like what I see about implementing a new filing system.
特別是我看到了這一段 「實施檔案管理系統」
Thank you.
謝謝
Filing system? Those colored labels you put on all the folders?
「檔案管理系統」？ 你說資料夾上黏的彩色標籤啊
It did brighten up the filing cabinets.
那的確是讓檔案櫃生色不少
They did more than that.
功能不只是那樣而已
I notice you've been entrusted with a lot of important responsibilities.
我看到你肩負了許多重要職責
Joanna really has been an incredible mentor to me.
對，喬安娜真是我的貴人
Rachel has been incredible at getting my bagels.
瑞秋也是幫我買焙果的貴人
She gets it right almost every time.
不可思議，她幾乎都不會買錯
Of course,I have more responsibilities than that.
我的職責當然不止那樣
Of course! There's the coffee too.
沒錯，還有咖啡也是
Rachel can carry two things at once.
瑞秋一次能拎兩樣東西
That's very good.
相當優秀
Now a big part of this job is...
這項工作的一大重點是
...cultivating personal relationships, especially with designers.
打好私人關係 尤其是和設計師
-Yes,l -She shouldn't have any problem.
對，我知道… 這一點瑞秋沒問題
Her only problem might be getting too friendly,you know?
只怕她打得太火熱了吧？
I love working with designers.
我最愛和設計師共事了
With them. Under them. What's the difference?
共事或共枕又有何差別呢？
My first review is out.
我第一篇美食評論上報了
The Chelsea Reporter.
赤爾夕通訊報
These used to keep me so warm.
以前我都拿這來當棉被蓋
Look,I'm on the back page.
快看，我寫的刊在反面
"Would I go back to Allesandro's? Sure,I'd get two meals.
我會再光顧「亞歷山卓」嗎？ 當然，但我會點兩份餐
One for me,and one for the guy pointing the gun to my head."
一份給自己 一份給拿槍抵著我的人
You really laid into this place.
你真把這家店批得一文不值
They don't pay me a penny a word to make friends.
報社付我錢 可不是要我廣結善緣
I found a guy who'd fix up the van for catering.
我得走了，我找到一個人 他能搞定那部外燴廂型車
You want me to go?
要我一起去嗎？
It's okay. Are we sure we don't want the waterbed?
不用了，沒關係 但你確定我們不要那張水床？
Because it would be silly to take it out if we're just gonna put it back in again.
如果拿下來又要放回去 那不是很蠢嗎？
Haven't we made this decision?
我們不是早就說好了？
Yeah,all right.
對啦，算了
再見 再見
-Who is it? -It's Allesandro,from Allesandro's.
誰啊？ 我是亞歷山卓的老闆
-Oh,my God. -I want to talk to you about your review.
天啊 我要跟你討論美食評鑒的事
Call me on the phone.
你打電話給我
What? So you can hang up on me?
好讓你掛我電話？
I'll never let you up, so just go away.
我不會讓你上來的 你還是走吧
-Just give me a chance to -Do you need to get in?
給我一個機會… 你要進來嗎？請進
No,Phoebe!
菲比，不行啦
Hey,Monica!
嗨，摩妮卡
I want a retraction. Our food is not "inedible swill."
我要你收回你的話 我們的食物絕非「難以下嚥」
I couldn't eat it.
我就吃不下去
My five friends couldn't eat it, and one of them eats books.
我那五個朋友也難以下嚥 其中一個人連書都能吃了
Our service isn't "grossly incompetent."
我們的服務 也不是賓至如「衰」
The waiter carried the breadsticks in his pants.
侍者把把麵包棒塞在褲子裡
Well,you said that we accept the Discover Card...
你還寫說 我們店裡接受發現卡
...which we do not!
其實不行
All right,that I'll retract.
好啊，那段話我可以收回
But I stand by my review. I know food,and that wasn't it.
但我捍衛我寫的評論 我懂美食，你們賣的差遠了
Your marinara sauce tastes like tomato juice.
你們的大蒜番茄醬 簡直跟蕃茄汁沒兩樣
You should serve it with vodka and celery.
應該要配伏特加 和芹菜莖一起上
I'm proud of that sauce. It's delicious.
我很以店裡那醬汁為榮 可口極了
You own an ltalian restaurant, and you think that tastes good?
天啊，你是開意大利餐廳的 竟然覺得那樣叫做可口？
Where are you from?
你到底是哪裡人？
Lebanon.
黎巴嫩
Hand me those tomatoes.
把那些蕃茄給我
I'll show you what it should taste like.
我來示範純正的味道是怎樣
How long will this take? I got another critic to yell at.
你要弄多久？ 我還要去罵另一個美食評論家
Joanna,I want to talk about that interview.
喬安娜，我要談談面試的事
I thought it went very well.
我覺得你在面試中表現得很棒
No,it didn't. That's what I want to talk to you about.
不，才怪 我就是要跟你說這件事
Now just to brief you...
我先聲明一句…
...I may cry.
我可能會哭出來
But they are not tears of sadness or of anger...
但那不是悲傷或氣憤的淚水
...but just of us having this discussion.
只是因為我要你跟討論這件事
Please,don't make a scene.
麻煩你別丟人現眼了
There's nobody here.
這裡又沒人
Sophie,get in here.
蘇菲，你進來
See? You're making Sophie uncomfortable.
看吧，你讓蘇菲尷尬了
No,she's not.
我沒有尷尬啊
Congratulations. You crossed the line into completely useless. Get out.
恭喜，你剛證明了 自己一無用處，滾吧
Do you want me to quit?
你是要我辭職嗎？
What makes you think that?
你怎麼會這樣想？
Those things you said in the interview...
因為你在面試時講的那些話
...if you believe them, I must not be a good assistant.
如果裡面有你的真心話 那我一定不是個好助理
You know what?
不如這樣吧
I am just going to pack up my desk...
我要來收拾辦公桌
...and I will be gone by the end of the day.
我等今天下班就走人
There's no use staying till the end of the day.
我想沒必要耗到今天下班了
Wait,wait.
你等等…
You can put your sad little muffin back.
把那可憐的鬆糕放回抽屜裡
If you must know the truth,I didn't want to lose a good assistant.
如果你要聽實話的話 是我不想失去你這完美的助理
What?
什麼？
That's why I said those things about your flirting and drinking.
所以我才瞎掰出那些招蜂引蝶 還有你酗酒的事
My drinking?
我酗酒？
I must have said that after you left.
我等你離開之後才說的
Said what,exactly?
你到底說了什麼？
You enjoy the occasional drink...
你三不五時喜歡喝一杯…
...-ing binge.
酒後亂性
Oh,my God! That is it. I'm leaving!
天啊，真是夠了，我走人
You are just a horrible person!
你這個人真的很糟糕
Wait,wait.
等等…
If you're going to get all sensitive about it.
反應不用那麼激烈嘛
I don't want to lose you.
我不想失去你
What if I create a position for you?
不如我變出個職位給你？
I'll make you assistant buyer in this department.
我讓你在這個部門裡 擔任採購助理
Say more things like that.
你再多說一點
Your own office and a raise, effective tomorrow.
你有自己的辦公室 外帶加薪，明天就生效
-I need an expense account. -Done!
我需要公關費 沒問題
-And an assistant. -Sophie!
還要有助理 蘇菲，進來
Hey,I thought you'd be out partying with Gandol-...
你們怎麼在這裡 不是跟甘呆夫…
...-dorf.
去狂歡了？
It's Gandalf,and he's not coming.
是甘道夫，他不來了
You've been sitting here all day?
那你們一早都呆坐在這裡？
I balanced my checkbook.
沒有，我剛剛把帳算好了
And I gave first names to all the foosball players.
對，手足球檯裡的選手 我也全都取好了名字
I can't believe he didn't come.
不敢相信甘道夫竟然沒來
So what? We can still go out and party ourselves.
他不來又怎樣？ 我們還是可以自己出去狂歡啊
With Gandalf,we'd be out all night.
有甘道夫在，一整晚都有的玩
We'd meet total strangers and hang out with them.
而且能和一堆陌生人一起混
We could do that.
我們也可以啊
There was other stuff too.
他還有其他的絕招啦
We'll do it all and better!
我們一網打盡，更勝於藍
After tonight,Gandalf will want to party with us,dude!
兄弟，今晚過後 就換我們帶甘道夫去狂歡
It's not like we don't know how to party!
活像我們不會狂歡似的
All right! Let's go.
好，咱們走
Maybe we could end up on a boat again?
最後再到一次船上如何？
All right!
好耶！
When were we on a boat?
上次在船上是何時？
Remember that cold morning with those dogs licking your face?
記得那天早上很冷 一早醒來還有狗舔你的臉？
Those were seals,man.
記得 老兄，舔你的可是海豹呢
How would this suit look on an assistant buyer
摩妮卡，快問快答 採購助理穿這套裝如何？
The owner of Allesandro's came to yell at me.
亞歷山卓的老闆上門來吼我
But I made him sauce,and he offered me the job as head chef!
但我乘勢幫他做了醬料 結果他挖我去店裡做主廚
You just ruined the thing I was practicing,but I'm so happy!
天啊，你毀了我練的好戲 但我真是替你高興
Can you believe it? I get to run my own kitchen!
你相信嗎？ 我終於可以在廚房當老大了
Oh,you've waited so long.
你盼了那麼久
Pheebs! Quick question for you.
菲比，快問快答
How would this suit look...
布魯明戴爾的採購助理…
...on an assistant buyer at Bloomingdale's?
穿上這套裝如何？
It would totally depend on her coloring and....
那完全要看她的膚色而定
You got the job!
你拿到那工作了！
You got the job? Why didn't you tell me?
你被錄取了？怎麼沒跟我說？
It'll be so great! I'll help decide what we sell.
一定超棒的 我能幫忙決定要賣什麼
I'll have an office with walls and everything.
還有全套裝潢的私人辦公室
I'm going to have walls!
四面都有牆耶
Is this the day of good news or what? I got us a job.
今天真是好消息連連 我幫大家找到工作了
The wedding reception.
喜宴外燴
I kind of need to talk to you about that.
菲比，我有話要跟你說
I think it's time for me to take a step back from the catering.
我想外燴的事不能操之過急
But we've only had one job.
但我們只做了一筆生意啊
But now we have this second one, and it feels like it's snowballing.
我知道，但現在有第二筆了 就像雪球越滾越大
What are you saying?
你在說什麼？
I got offered the head chef job at Allesandro's.
亞歷山卓餐廳請我去當主廚
It's okay,because you don't really need me.
什麼？ 不礙事的，仔細想想 其實你也不需要我
You're the cook!
廚師是你耶！
Without you,it's just me driving up to people's houses...
總不能我自己一個開去別人家
...with empty trays, asking for money.
帶著空盤子就跟人要錢吧？
All right. But I'll pay you back all the money you invested.
好，我會還回所有你投資的錢
-And you can keep the van! -For what?
那部廂型車歸你 我要拿來幹嘛？
I can't believe this!
我真是不敢相信
I got to get out of here.
我得離開這裡
Phoebe,wait a minute.
菲比，你等等
I'm an assistant buyer!
我升採購助理了！
（中央咖啡館）
We'll get coffee,get energized, then head back out.
我們先喝咖啡養足精神 再重新出動
-Yeah,all right. -Okay.
好吧 好
So we're having fun,right?
很好玩嘛，對不對？
We don't need that wizard guy.
我們才不需要那個什麼巫師的
We hit some clubs, talk to some strangers...
我們去了幾家俱樂部 跟一些陌生人說過話
...then go down to the docks and see about that boat thing.
等一下去碼頭安排坐船的事
I'm kind of beat.
我有點累了
Actually...
其實…
...me too.
我也是
Are you serious?
你們是真的假的？ 真的
Thank God! I'm exhausted.
感謝老天，我也累斃了
You guys want coffees?
你們要喝咖啡嗎？ 對
I don't want to be up too late, so I'll have a decaf.
但我今天想早點睡 所以我要無咖啡因的
Yeah,me too.
對，我也是
Actually,could I get some hot water with lemon?
我能來杯熱水加點萊姆汁嗎？
I strained my voice screaming in there. Does it have to be so loud?
我剛才在那家店裡都喊到啞了 他們音樂非要開那麼大聲嗎？
I can't hear a word. My ears are ringing so bad.
我聽不到你說什麼 我耳鳴得厲害
I was glad I had that extra pair of socks.
幸好我多帶了一雙襪子
I used them as mittens.
拿來當手套用
I didn't want to touch a thing in that last place.
最後那家店髒到我不敢用手碰
How sad are we?
我們真是可悲到了極點
Yeah,I know.
對，我知道
You know what? We're not sad.
其實我們並不可悲
We're just not 21 anymore. You know?
只是我們都過了21歲
I'm 29 years old,damn it!
我都已經29歲了
I want to sit in a comfortable chair,watch TV...
只想舒服地坐著看電視
...and go to sleep at a reasonable hour.
時間到了就上床睡覺
I like to hang out in a quiet place where I can talk to my friends.
我喜歡去安靜一點的地方 才能好好跟朋友聊天
And so what if I like to go home, put on Kenny G and take a bath?
就算回家聽肯尼吉的音樂洗澡 又有什麼大不了？
We're 29. We're not women.
我們是29歲沒錯 但我們可不是娘兒們
There you are.
你到了
I'm glad you decided to hear me out.
我很高興你決定聽我解釋
Okay,I'm hearing.
好，你說吧
I've been doing a lot of thinking.
我想了很多
I came up with a bunch of businesses that you can do with your van.
我想出了你用廂型車 可以做的所有生意
You could be a flower delivery person.
你可以去送花
-What? -Or a bakery delivery person?
什麼？ 或是送麵包？
Pizza?
送比薩？
摩妮卡？
I got a whole bunch of stuff in this area.
我寫了一堆你能運送的東西
But I get the feeling you don't want to deliver.
但我有預感你不想送貨
-No. -Okay.
對 那好吧
I guess if you don't want to deliver...
我猜若你不想送貨的話…
...you probably don't want to pick up stuff either.
八成也不會想去載貨
No.
對
You know what?
不如這樣吧
Let's do the catering business.
我們來做外燴
-Really? Are you sure? -Yeah,I made a commitment to you.
真的？你確定？ 對，我承諾過你
It'd be fun.
會很有趣的
It will be fun!
一定會很有趣的
Let's plan the wedding reception.
那我們來計劃喜宴的事
You really wanted me to do something with this van.
你還真的是很用心想了 讓我用這廂型車來做些事
You know what? I want you to take the chef job.
不如這樣吧 我要你接下那主廚的工作
-Really? -Yeah.
真的？ 對
That's what you really want.
那是你真心想要做的
I don't want to be the reason you're unhappy. I'd be unhappy.
我不想成為你不高興的原因 那樣我也會不高興
And I really don't want to be the reason I'm unhappy.
我更不想讓自己不高興
Thank you.
謝謝你
Besides,it might be kind of fun to form the new A-Team.
而且成立新的天龍特攻隊 應該會很好玩
Hi,Mrs. Lynch.
林區太太
Is Joanna in already?
喬安娜進公司了嗎？
Oh,my goodness! You haven't heard.
老天，你還沒聽說
-Heard what? -Joanna...
聽說什麼？ 喬安娜…
...passed away last night.
昨晚過世了
Oh,my God! How?
天啊，怎麼會這樣？
She was leaving work, and she was hit by a cab.
她下班出去時被計程車撞上
Oh,my God! I cannot believe it!
天啊，我不敢相信
I know.
我知道
Oh,God. Oh,God.
天啊…
Oh,God.
天啊
I didn't realize that you were so close.
沒想到你們兩個這麼好
Yes. So close!
對，好到不行 （亦指：就差那麼一點點）
I know that this is an emotional and difficult time for all of us.
林區太太，我知道這個節骨眼 大家在情緒上都很煎熬
But by any chance,did Joanna...
但在事發之前，喬安娜是不是…
...send any paperwork your way before...
...正好有把人事調動公文…
-...it happened? -No,nothing.
..交給你？ 完全沒有
Imagine,if she'd just stepped off that curb a few seconds later.
只盼當初 她晚個幾秒鐘過街就沒事了
Yes,just a few seconds and she'd still be with us.
對，差個幾秒鐘 她就還能跟我們在一起
Nothing about an assistant buyer?
她沒說到採購助理的事？
I'm sorry. I have to go.
不好意思，我得走了
Good morning!
早安
I guess you didn't hear about Joanna.
蘇菲，我猜你還不知道 喬安娜的事
I sure did!
我當然知道
I'm excited about having Monica on board with us.
我很興奮能請到摩妮卡加入
Although I do feel bad about having fired Chef Emilio.
雖然開除艾米裡歐主廚 讓我覺得很過意不去
It is like losing a member of the family.
那就像是失去了一個家人
Of course,that literally is the case for several of you.
不過對你們其中幾位而言 真的是失去家人
Tony,Carlos,Marie...
東尼、卡洛斯、瑪莉…
...please tell your father how much we're going to miss him.
請向令尊轉達 我們會有多想念艾米裡歐
I know Monica has a lot of great ideas for this place.
我知道摩妮卡對這家店 有許多很棒的點子
Well,you all read the review.
你們都看過她那篇評論了
So without much further ado...
所以廢話不多說
...I present to you our new head chef.
在此向各位介紹本店的新主廚
I just want to say that with a pinch of excitement...
我只想說只要有熱忱
...a dash of hard work and a dollop of cooperation...
肯吃苦，肯合作
...we can have the recipe....
我們就能將本店的菜色…
Are you going to kill me?
你們打算殺我滅口？